# TRINH TIEN PHAT

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

## Summary

As a Front-End Developer, I'm constantly pushing the boundaries of what's possible in web development. With a strong foundation in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Tailwind, and SCSS, I'm ready to take on any challenge and help create amazing online experiences.

**1** 0938.068.917

phattien991412@gmail.com

Ba Diem, Hoc Mon, TPHCM

https://tienphat-portfolio.netlify.app

### Tech Stack

- HTML & CSS
- Javascript
- ReactJs
- NextJs
- Redux
- SASS
- TailwindCss
- Antd
- ChakraUI
- GSAP

### Education

#### UNIVERSITY OF TRANSPORT HCM

**Auto Mechanics** 

2017 - 2021

### CYBERSOFT ACADEMY

Front-end Course

03/2021 - 10/2021

### Language

English - Toeic 650

### Experience

### INTER FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Cong Ty CP CN & KT Stech

08/2022 - 11/2022

Participated in the development of the Dakshow project, focusing on studying and updating the UI and creating new functions.

#### FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Cong Ty CP CN & KT Stech

11/2022 - present

- Continuously participated in the development of the Dakshow project by creating and optimizing code and enhancing functionality.
- Collaborated with the BE team to create and update APIs.
- Build a core service to manage APIs.
- Contributed to building the company's websites:
  - Stechvn website: https://stechvn.org
  - Welcome Dakshow website: https://welcome.dakshow.com
  - ICO website
  - CMS for Dakshow

#### **PORTFOLIO**

Personal project

3 weeks

- My portfolio, wheret you can get more infomation about me.
- Visit page via link: https://tienphat-portfolio.netlify.app.
- Technology: HTML/SASS, Javascript, ReactJs, GSAP, ChakraUI

#### **SOCIAL MEDIA GUIDE**

Personal project

2 days

- A clone UI of social media guide, idea from E-Commerce Nation.
- Feature: Change the layout by choosing a social option or using the search feature.
- Technology: HTML/SASS, Javascript, ReactJs, ChakraUI
- Visit page via link: https://socialguide47.netlify.app/